

PETER WILMSHURST

Senior Front End Developer









I am a senior frontend developer with 10+ years of commercial experience. I'm interested in all kinds of visual communication, but my major focus is on the design and development of web, mobile & tablet interfaces. I am enthusiastic, self-motivated and extremely driven with a wide range of skills both in terms of design and development.

Skills/Experience













Markdown





Grunt



NPM



LESS



Javascript

React



Node













Terminal

Apple

Microsoft

Adobe

GitHub

Wordpress

Magento

Bootstrap

Atlassian

Mailchimp

SASS

Agile

Employment

Senior Frontend Developer | Domtar Personal Care | April 2015 - Present

Core member of a multi-disciplinary digital team, delivering enhancements and maintenance across all digital properties, company wide.

Graphic Designer | Attends | February 2013 - April 2015

Working with a small team to maintain multiple global healthcare brands. Producing artwork, POS, print and digital marketing materials.

Creative Web Developer | Website Success | August 2009 - February 2013

Design and development of websites, from static HTML to fully fledged ecommerce business solutions. Manage and present web strategies whilst providing customer support and maintenance.

Freelance Designer | Peter Wilmshurst | 2002 - 2009

Web design and development, print design, video and animation services

Education

University of Portsmouth | 2003 - 2007

Bachelor of Science Degree in Computer Games Technology Areas of study: Computer 3D/2D Animation, Video Game/Web Development, Computer Languages, Motion Capture.

St. Vincent College | 2000 - 2002

3 x A Levels, 2 x AS Levels in Graphic Design (A Level), Communication Studies (A Level), Psychology (AS Level), General Studies (AS Level), Computing (A Level).

Bay House School | 1995 - 2000

10 x GCSE's in English Language, English Literature, German, Electronics, Maths, Geography, Science (double award), Art and Business Studies.